Million viewers are going to Hinder this and say
数以百万计的观众对此表示怀疑
Second-hand diving shark news
二手潜水鲨鱼新闻
It's been a long time
已经很久了
I want to go home with all my
我想和我一起回家
This looks like a job for me
这对我来说似乎是一份工作
Give me some
给我一些
Particularly
尤其
I think so
我认同
Oyster is now
牡蛎现在
Akash open
阿卡什开
And then if I had crazy glue
然后如果我有疯狂的胶水
I could put it this shell back together
我可以把它放回去
Is no problem
没问题
I think is good
我觉得很好
Favourite things in the entire world
全世界最喜欢的东西
Nothing really sorry just want to do
没什么好抱歉的，只是想做
Women
妇女
Just on my way around and tell her
就在我身边告诉她
Massage to get juicy there I need his leg
按摩使多汁，我需要他的腿
In one Swift move
一举一动
Circle wall around it
围绕它围墙
From the shelf
从架子上
Oyster here you can always identify an oyster is having a blue top and a bottom
牡蛎在这里您始终可以确定牡蛎的顶部和底部为蓝色
Changeable upside is going to be the bottom shelf in the flat inside is going to be the Top Shop
可变的上升空间将成为平整内部的最底层货架，并将成为顶级商店
To come in at the points and we're going to find the hinge is probably a good idea to wear a bra
进入要点，我们将发现铰链可能是戴胸罩的好主意
Non dominant hand
非优势手
The Quays opening Easter is about twisting not pushed into the head
码头开放复活节是关于扭曲而不是推入头部
Go back and forth until you feel the open up there
来回走动直到感觉到那里的开放
Manhole disguise
沙井伪装
I'm going to try the note
我要去试一试
The inside of the top shelf slide in between
顶部搁板的内部在两者之间滑动
And slide ride across that does this separate the muscle of the Oyster
滑行，可以分开牡蛎的肌肉
From the shell on a
从外壳上
Ok so that my
好，这样我的
Easter is
复活节是
Nicely preserved on the inside
很好地保存在里面